{
    "id": "15cfc37a50474494a1233e56447dbd37",
    "title": "Adverbs With Two Forms",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Sorry I didn’t turn up – I ……………….. forgot.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "clean",
                "cleanly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f9960d4aef7849a6accca880b63174db"
        },
        {
            "question": "At least ten children were ……………….. injured in the accident.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "deadly",
                "fatally"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c812c8f4e2a44fd888905a68b00d73cb"
        },
        {
            "question": "The comedy show was ………………….. amusing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "high",
                "highly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0b01f165c012450a842e667b5fa2e13e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The protestors demanded that the culprits should be ………………….  punished.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "just",
                "justly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "627094a352b24ba9b5ec80f2f6fe2a26"
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t been to the theater much ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "late",
                "lately"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "12a664ffe55a427ebad2d26d5cba976e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Isn’t she dressed …………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pretty",
                "prettily"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2616b9ce4695415886704b41a7192825"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will be there at six o’clock ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sharp",
                "sharply"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8f0a3962cf364405a2f019b4aa31f2a7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Their door was ………………… open but nobody was inside.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wide",
                "widely"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c0c6b90d596640c3bd5613c7a4aa7d55"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. believed that she loved me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wrong",
                "wrongly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7d8e04c94fff43bf80e60b9d8a1183d4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hate arriving …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "late",
                "lately"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8f8acaa516944fbb8acce52af387b8c9"
        }
    ]
}